const quiz = [
  {
    question: 'Which is the strongest tarot card?',
    option1: ' The Star',
    option2: ' The Fool',
    option3: ' The Moon',
    option4: ' The Sun',
    answer: ' The Fool',
  },

  {
    question:
      'The Six of Swords, Lord of Earned Success, is symbolic of which of the following when in the upright orientation?',
    option1: ' Carefree living',
    option2: ' Earned success',
    option3: ' Gradual change',
    option4: ' Overpowering of enemies',
    answer: ' Gradual change',
  },

  {
    question:
      'How many total cards are there in tarot?',
    option1: ' 22',
    option2: ' 56',
    option3: ' 78',
    option4: ' none of the above',
    answer: ' 78',
  },

  {
    question: 'Which tarot card means good fortune?',
    option1: ' The Star',
    option2: ' The Moon',
    option3: ' The Fool',
    option4: ' The Sun',
    answer: ' The Star',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which card represents the Child of the Forces of Time?',
    option1: ' The Hermit',
    option2: ' The Magician',
    option3: ' The Devil',
    option4: ' Wheel of Fortune',
    answer: ' The Devil',
  },
  {
    question: 'In the upright orientation, what does The Fool represent?',
    option1: ' Beginnings',
    option2: ' Innocence and naivety',
    option3: ' Ill-advised risks',
    option4: ' Forgiveness',
    answer: ' Beginnings',
  },
  {
    question:
      'The knight of which suit represents a stoic and indifferent person in the upright orientation?',
    option1: ' Swords',
    option2: ' Pentacles',
    option3: ' Cups',
    option4: ' Wands',
    answer: ' Pentacles',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following, when in the reverse orientation, means the closest thing to the Two of Cups in the reverse orientation?',
    option1: ' The Sun',
    option2: ' King of Pentacles',
    option3: ' Three of Swords',
    option4: ' The Hanged Man',
    answer: ' The Sun',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What does the Strength card symbolize in the reverse orientation?',
    option1: ' Powerlessness',
    option2: ' Poor judgment',
    option3: ' Lack of self-control',
    option4: ' Power wrongly used',
    answer: ' Power wrongly used',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the most powerful card in the Tarot?',
    option1: ' The Fool',
    option2: ' Wheel of Fortune',
    option3: ' The Magician',
    option4: ' The Sun',
    answer: ' The Fool',
  },
];

export default quiz;
